realtourvision.com 2014-07-01

# Privacy Policy | RTV 360 Software

**Updated: 2/12/2008**

Tour Vision Inc, is a Michigan corporation with its principal office at 400 E Eighth Street, Suite 2, Traverse City, MI 49686 (d.b.a. RTV) and hereinafter referred to as "RTV", or "Company".

This privacy statement covers the Web site www.realtourvision.com. Because RTV wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, we have provided the below listed information and privacy practices for your review. Our Privacy Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect and use the personal information you provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using our site and our products and services.

## What Information Do We Collect?

When you visit our Web site you may provide us with two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected on an individual basis and Web site use information collected on an aggregate basis as you and others browse our Web site.

### 1\. Personal Information You Choose to Provide

**Registration Information/Purchase Information**

You will provide us information about yourself, your firm or company, and your practices when you (1) place an order for one our products or services; or (2) register to be a member of RTV Dealer Network, register for certain services, or register for email newsletters and alerts, or purchase items through our site. This data collection can include such personally identifiable information as name, company name, address, phone number, email address, and credit card information. You may also provide additional comments on how you see RTV servicing your needs and interests.

**Email Information.**

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses.

### 2\. Web Site Use Information

Similar to other commercial Web sites, our Web site utilizes a standard Web server logs to collect information about how our Web site is used. Information gathered through Web server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our Web site, and the Web sites visited just before and just after our Web site. We, our advertisers and ad serving companies may also use small technology or pieces of code to determine which advertisements and promotions users have seen and how users responded to them. Personally identifiable information is not stored in these logs. We log files to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate, usage and volume statistic to help us better understand the needs of our visitors.

**How Do We Use the Information That You Provide to Us?**

Broadly speaking, we use personal information for purposes of administering and expanding our business activities, providing customer service and making available other products and services to our customers and prospective customers. Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. You have the opportunity to opt in, or opt out of these specific types of communications in Tour Management System. You have the opportunity to opt out any time you receive an email from us by using the link provided at the bottom of the email communication. You may notify us at any time if you do not wish to receive these offers by emailing us at support@realtourvision.com.

**Communications from our Site/Choice-Opt Out**

If you register on our site or purchase any products from the site you can expect to receive a welcome email and /or an order confirmation email. If you have registered with our site, you will also receive any of the communications (newsletters, updates, product information, alerts) that the Company sends to its Dealer network. At any time you wish to change your preferences for receiving communications from our site, please edit your records in the Tour Management System or contact Customer Support.

**Blogs**

If you use our blogs, your should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there, name/Web site, can be read, collected, or used by other users in this forum. We are not responsible for the personal information you choose to submit in the blogs.

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**

We may enter into alliances, partnerships or other business arrangements with third parties who may be given access to personal information including your name, address, telephone number and email for the purpose of providing you information regarding products and services that we think will be of interest to you. In connection with alliances, partnerships or arrangements, we may also provide certain information to third parties if we have determined that the information will be used in a responsible manner by a responsible third party. For example, some of our partners operate stores or provide services on our site, while others power offerings developed by us for your use. We also use third parties to facilitate our business, including, but not limited to, sending email and processing credit card payments. In connection with these offerings and business operations, our partners and other third parties may have access to your personal information for use in connection with business activities. As we develop our business, we may buy or sell assets or business offerings. Customer, email, and visitor information is generally one of the transferred business assets in these types of transactions. We may also transfer such information in the course of corporate divestitures, mergers, or any dissolution.

**Notice of New Services and Changes**

Occasionally, we may also use the information we collect to notify you about important changes to our Web site, new services and special offers we think you will find valuable. As our customer, you will be given the opportunity to notify us of your desire not to receive these offers by sending us an email request at support@realtourvision.com.

**Email-A-Friend/Tour**

If you choose to use the Email a Friend or Email a Tour referral service to tell a friend about information you've seen on our site, we will ask you for your friend's email address and any comment you wish to make to your friend. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email forwarding the requested tour or information. We do not store this information and it is used for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email.

## 3\. How Do We Protect Your Information?

**How Do We Secure Information Transmissions?**

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. Some of the information you may enter on our Web site may be transmitted securely via Secure Sockets Layer SSL, 128 bit encryption services. Pages utilizing this technology will have URLs that start with HTTPS instead of HTTP.

**How Can You Access and Correct Your Information?**

You may request access to all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain in our database by accessing your account details in the Tour Management System

**Certain Disclosures**

We may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or subpoena or if we believe that such action is necessary to (a) conform to the law or comply with legal process served on us or affiliated parties; (b) protect and defend our rights and property, our site, the users of our site, and/or our affiliated parties; (c) act under circumstances to protect the safety of users of our site, us, or third parties.

**What About Other Web Sites Linked to Our Web Site?**

We are not responsible for the practices employed by Web sites linked to or from our Web site nor the information or content contained therein. Often links to other Web sites are provided solely as pointers to information on topics that may be useful to the users of our Web site.

Please remember that when you use a link to go from our Web site to another Web site, our Privacy Policy is no longer in effect. Your browsing and interaction on any other Web site, including Web sites which have a link on our Web site, is subject to that Web site’s own rules and policies. Please read over those rules and policies before proceeding.

**Your Consent**

By using our Web site you consent to our collection and use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on our Web site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it.
